# **CHONG TUN AN**

## 3D Designer/Unity developer

Address PETALING JAYA, SELANGOR, 47300

Phone +601121054753

**Emall** duon94010104@gmail.com

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/tun-an-chong-843206199

### **PORTFOLIO**

https://gduon.github.lo/







#### Skill

Proficient in Blender, Unity, 3ds MAX, Photoshop, After Effect Fluent in Sketchup, Autocad, Visual Studio code, HTML5 web

#### About me

Self motivated 3D Designer with added experience of Unity3D development. Adept at bringing new life to existing characters and environment. Versed in multiple program such as Blender, 3ds Max and Unity. Keen eye for resolving problem and always ready to adept and improve.

#### Work history

#### 3D Designer, Laconix Resource Sdn Bhd, Kota Damansara

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

- Help in pushing the growth and expand of company as the sole independent 3D designer.
- Introduce and integrate new technique to improve on company work flow.
- Tack on project that differ from company usual job scope and were able to acquire the deal with client on first time.
- Effectively communicate with company sales team while recommending solution regarding project design and budget limitation.
- Communicated with supervisor to brainstorm ideas and discuss upcoming projects.

#### 3D Designer, Ace Above Creative Event, Desa Park City

Oct 2021 - March 2022

- Work closely with event sales team and designer to produce stage/pros design, layout planning that cover variety of event such as company launching, annual dinner, conference etc.
- Role as company main 3D visualize output, event layout planning, occasional animation when need arise.
- In charge of designing company latest 3D virtual platform that serve as templated for virtual event commission by various party.

### Freelance/Part time 3D Artist, Self employed, Petaling Jaya

April 2022 – Present

 Sketch and produce realistic 3D render consist of interior design, product design, menu catalogue 3D visual, manufacture etc.

#### Education

Diploma in Landscape Architecture, Infrastructure University Kuala Lumpur, Kajang

### Language

- English
- Mandarin
- Malay